RENUKA KAMATH

Full Stack Developer

https://renukakamath.github.io/portfolio

+91 9495795304 renukakamath2@gmail.com kochi , kerala

ABOUT

I am a passionate full stack developer having expertise of 1 + years. I work closely with my clients in developing strong brand identities that define and exhibit values, and also professional visual entities to define your tone. I am a strong team player and a social butterfly.

SKILLS

PROFICENT WITH: • HTML • CSS • PHP • ANDROID JAVA • PYTHON • MYSQL

FAMILIAR WITH: •Node.js• MongoDB • Express.js •GitHub Actions

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software development, Riss Technologies & freelancer

Aug 2023 - Present

Part Time - Website/Application Designing & Website/Application Developing

Software Associate, Riss Technologies

June 2022 - Aug 2023

Designing & Develop Web/App interfaces -Riss Technologies, Cochin Enthusiastic and driven
, i have a deep passion for software development. Through 1 years 2 month of practice and
many personal projects

Self - Study 2019 - 2022

 Designing & Develop Web ,As I am mostly a self-leaner , I can easily adapt to new things and always ready to take on a challenge

EDUCATION

MASTER IN COMPUTER APPLICATION

Aug 2023 - Present

Kalam Technological University Sree Narayana Gurukulam College Of Engineering kochi kerala

BACHELOR IN COMPUTER APPLICATION

2019 - 2022

BCA- Cochin Arts & Science kochi kerala Under Mahatma Gandhi University

PROJECTS

• E-COMMERCE Website - Online Cosmetic Shop , Online Watch Shop

Technologies used: html, css, javascript, bootstrap,php,mysql Link to GitHub repo:

Online Cosmetic Shop: https://github.com/renukakamath/cosmetic_shop_py.git

Online Watch Shop: https://github.com/renukakamath/watch_php.git

• Traveling APP - Smart travel Guide(blockchain project)

block chain is user in payment section.

Technologies used: html,css,javascript,bootstrap,python ,android java ,mysql , blockchain Link to GitHub repo: https://github.com/renukakamath/metroticket_py.git

• Room decorator - colour myworld

Technologies used: html, css, javascript,bootstrap,python,android java,mysql Link to GitHub repo:https://github.com/renukakamath/colormyworld_py.git